The dizzying variety of options, the amazing range of flavours, and for some of us, the sheer quantity that you can eat.
令人眼花缭乱的餐品选择、丰富多样的口味，对我们有些人而言，还有可以尽情享用的海量食物。
It's easy to see the appeal of a buffet. It takes the stress out of choosing what to eat - just have it all!
自助餐的魅力显而易见，它省去了挑选食物的纠结——想吃什么尽管拿就好！
But are there risks that we need to think about?
但我们是否需要留意其中潜藏的风险？
Food hygiene specialists suggest there might be.
食品卫生专家表示，或许确实存在这类风险。
Restaurant and hotel buffets can be a food poisoning risk.
餐厅和酒店的自助餐可能存在食物中毒风险。
The large number of different dishes and people serving themselves creates opportunities for cross-contamination.
大量不同的菜肴以及人们自己取餐，造成了交叉污染的机会。
Microbes can be transferred from people to dishes, from dishes to people and from one dish to another.
微生物可以从人传播到菜肴，从菜肴传播到人，以及从一道菜传播到另一道菜。
Even the air can transfer microbes to your food.
甚至空气也能将微生物传播到你的食物上。
It's easy to see how an entire buffet could end up contaminated.
不难看出整个自助餐最终是如何被污染的。
Food temperature creates another risk factor.
食物温度是另一个风险因素。
It's easy for food to be kept lukewarm and in the danger zone between 8C and 63C where bacteria and other microbes grow and multiply easily.
食物很容易被保持在微温状态，处于8°C到63°C之间的危险区域，细菌和其他微生物在此温度下容易生长和繁殖。
Restaurants that manage buffets well can reduce the risks.
管理得当的自助餐厅可以降低风险。
Hot food should be replaced after two hours and cold food after four.
热食应在两小时后更换，冷食应在四小时后更换。
It's important that the old food is disposed of and that containers are not just topped up, allowing the older food to contaminate fresh items.
重要的是，旧食物要被处理掉，容器不能只是加满，以免旧食物污染新鲜食物。
Hot food should be kept above 63C, and cold food should be refrigerated.
热食应保持在63°C以上，冷食应冷藏。
However, any attempts by hospitality businesses to reduce risks can easily be undone by careless clients.
然而，餐饮企业为降低风险所做的任何努力，都可能被粗心的顾客轻易破坏。
There are many ways that diners can unwittingly or thoughtlessly increase the risks.
用餐者有许多方式会在无意或考虑不周的情况下增加风险。
Tongs and ladles can be contaminated by those who do not wash their hands, or who reuse their plates when getting a second helping.
夹子和勺子可能被不洗手的人，或者在第二次取餐时重复使用盘子的人污染。
Food on display can be contaminated by people using the wrong utensil or who accidentally drop the handles into bowls of food.
展示的食物可能被使用错误餐具或不小心将手柄掉入食物碗中的人污染。
That's before even mentioning those who cough or sneeze near the buffet.
这还不包括那些在自助餐附近咳嗽或打喷嚏的人。
So, to enjoy a buffet, while keeping the risks as low as possible, you should check to see that it is well-managed by the restaurant or hotel, that others are following good hygiene rules and that you do the same.
因此，为了享受自助餐，同时尽可能降低风险，你应该检查餐厅或酒店是否管理得当，其他人是否遵守良好的卫生规则，并且你自己也要这样做。
Even so, a buffet is likely to be more risky than other types of restaurants.
即便如此，自助餐还是可能比其他类型的餐厅风险更高。